lemonstand.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | LemonStand

### Introduction

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to the lemonstandapp.com website.

LemonStand eCommerce Inc. is committed to respecting and protecting your online privacy. We have established this Online Privacy Policy in order for you to understand our policies with regard to your personal information.

#### Gathering and Use of Information

LemonStand eCommerce Inc. will only collect your personal information when you purchase our products, register for early versions of our products, or when you voluntarily sign-up for a membership account in order to access certain areas of our site, or when you sign-up for our mailing list. Access to our web site is mostly unrestricted, and you may browse the majority of it anonymously.

#### Cookies

Our website utilizes "cookies". A "cookie" is a small text file that permits us to recognize your browser in order to customize your experience, or permit you to access restricted areas. Cookies do not contain personal information.

#### IP Address

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you access the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to gather broad demographic information.

#### Mailing Lists

As a member of our Web site you may occasionally receive an email newsletter informing you of new products, services or news. You may choose not to receive further email messages by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom and/or top of the email.

#### Commitment

We are committed to privacy and support industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Questions about this can be directed to us though our Contact page.

×

##  Log In 

To access your account
